Guide to the Capital Planning Building Files and Records 1981-1999
Washington State University Libraries Manuscripts, Archives, and Special Collections
- Building 9500 - Tri-Cities University Center Addition
  - General Correspondence #6 11/1/1990 - 3/31/1991 (Box 17)
  - General Correspondence #5 6/1/1990 - 10/31/1990 (Box 18)
  - General Correspondence #4 1/1/1990 - 5/31/1990 (Box 18)
  - General Correspondence #3 1/1/1989 - 12/31/1989 (Box 18)
  - General Correspondence #2 5/1/1988 - 12/31/1988 (Box 18)
  - General Correspondence #1 1/1/1987 - 4/1/1988 (Box 18)
  - McKinley Gordon General Correspondence #14 11/1/1991 - 1/31/1992 (Box 18)
  - McKinley Gordon General Correspondence #13 9/1/1991 - 10/31/1991 (Box 18)
  - McKinley Gordon General Correspondence #12 8/1/1991 - 8/30/1991 (Box 18)
  - McKinley Gordon General Correspondence #11 6/1/1991 - 7/31/1991 (Box 18)
  - McKinley Gordon General Correspondence #10 4/1/1991 - 5/31/1991 (Box 18)
  - McKinley Gordon General Correspondence #9 3/1/1991 - 4/30/1991 (Box 19)
  - McKinley Gordon General Correspondence #8 1/1/1991 - 2/28/1991 (Box 19)
  - McKinley Gordon General Correspondence #7 11/1/1990 - 12/31/1990 (Box 19)
  - McKinley Gordon General Correspondence #6 9/1/1990 - 10/31/1990 (Box 19)
  - McKinley Gordon General Correspondence #5 8/1/1990 - 8/31/1990 (Box 19)
  - McKinley Gordon General Correspondence #4 2/1/1990 - 7/30/1990 (Box 19)
  - McKinley Gordon General Correspondence #3 8/1/1989 - 2/28/1990 (Box 19)
  - McKinley Gordon General Correspondence #2 1/1/1989 - 7/31/1989 (Box 19)
  - McKinley Gordon General Correspondence #1 7/1/1987 - 12/31/1988 (Box 19)
  - McKinley Gordon Contract File #2 CO9119 10/1/1990 - 7/31/1992 (Box 19)
  - Branch Campus Development Alternatives Appendix for Chapter 7 (Box 21)
  - Chapter 7 Branch Campus Development WHECB 11/5/1989 (Box 21)
  - Riley Engineering, Inc. Life Cycle Cost Analysis January, 1989 (Box 21)
  - Dillman - Luvaas Architects Life Benefit and Life Cycle Cost Analysis (Box 21)
  - McKinley Gordon WSU Tn - Cities Design Development 3/7/198 9 (Box 21)
  - Material Data Safety Sheets, Miscellaneous Items various dates (Box 21)
  - Draft Tri-Cities University Center Building Addition 11/24/1987 (Box 21)
  - Draft Tri-Cities University Center Building Addition 12/30/1987 (Box 21)
  - Draft Tri-Cities University Center Building Addition 2/8/1988 (Box 21)
  - Tri-Cities University Center Building Addition 2/8/1988 (Box 21)
  - Addendum to Building Program 7/1/1988 (Box 21)
  - McKinley Gordon Draft Master Planning Report 5/4/1988 (Box 21)
  - Draft Master Planning Report 6/1/1988 (Box 21)
  - Master Planning Report 6/1/1988 (Box 21)
  - McKinley Gordon Schematic Design Building Statistics 8/22/1988 (Box 21)
  - McKinley Gordon Schematic Design Cost Estimate 8/22/1988 (Box 21)
  - McKinley Gordon Schematic Design 9/16/1988 (Box 21)
  - McKinley Gordon Field Reports 6/19/1991 - 8/14/1991 (Box 21)
  - State of WA Supplemental Proposal to the Advisory Council (Box 21)
  - Campus Reports various dates (Box 21)
  - Joint Center for Graduate Study Faculty Handbook 11/20/1981 (Box 21)
  - University Center Addition Travel Related Items (Box 21)
  - University Center Addition Travel Related Items Center Grad Study - Richland (Box 22)
  - Department of Capital Planning and Development (Box 22)
  - Commons Offices (Box 22)
- Building #0806 - Beasley Coliseum Asbestos Removal
  - Budget 2/26/1992 - 12/02/1992 (Box 22)
  - Environmental Impact Statement 1/13/1992 - 2/18/1992 (Box 22)
  - Regents 10/16/1992 (Box 22)
  - General Correspondence 4/29/1991 - 1/7/1994 (Box 22)
  - Alpha Engineers General Correspondence 6/1991 (Box 22)
  - Alpha Engineers Contract File no contents (Box 22)
- Communication Infrastructure Renewal (C.I.R.)
  - Budget 9/17/1991 - 12/19/1995 (Box 23)
  - Environmental Impact Statement 3/9/1992 - 5/20/1992 (Box 23)
  - Regents Reports 11/18/1991 - 5/11/1995 (Box 23)
  - Burke/Lee Correspondence 4/17/1992 - 9/27/1992 (Box 23)
  - Robert Fossatti Associates 11/24/1993 (Box 23)
  - Mahan and DeS alvo Correspondence 3/19/1992 - 7/31/1992 (Box 23)
  - Installation Operational Contract - Johnson Controls Network Integration Svcs. 6/7/1994 (Box 23)
  - Program Committee 6/10/1992 - 9/30/1994 (Box 23)
  - Facilities Work Group #3 10/1/1992 - 5/12/1993 (Box 23)
  - Construction Reports 9/15/1993 - 9/17/1993 (Box 23)
  - General Correspondence #6 7/1/1994 - 10/4/1996 (Box 23)
  - JWP Information Systems, Inc. General Correspondence 4/9/1992 - 11/9/1993 (Box 23)
  - JWP Information Systems, Inc. Contract File C0 10714 11/20/1992 - 12/18/1992 (Box 23)
  - Inland Construction, Inc. General Correspondence 9/16/1994 - 11/18/1994 (Box 23)
  - Inland Construction, Inc. Contract File CO 11790 9/1/1994 - 10/6/1994 (Box 23)
  - Poe Asphalt Paving, Inc. Contract File CO 11643 8/4/1994 - 7/12/1995 (Box 23)
  - Shea Construction, Inc. General Correspondence 5/24/1994 - 9/28/1994 (Box 23)
  - Shea Construction, Inc. Contract File CO 11642 4/12/199 (Box 23)
  - Rejected Bids - Telecomm Equipment Rooms - Bid Date 9/1/1994 (Box 23)
  - Rejected Bids - Satellite Master Antennae TV - Bid Date 7/26/1994 (Box 23)
  - Rejected Bids - Five Main Communication Facility - Bid Date 2/25/1994 (Box 23)
  - Facilities Work Group #2 6/1/1992 - 9/30/1992 (Box 23)
  - Facilities Work Group #1 12/31/1991 - 5/31/1992 (Box 23)
  - General Correspondence #5 2/1/1994 - 6/30/1994 (Box 23)
  - General Correspondence #4 12/1/1994 - 1/31/1994 (Box 23)
  - General Correspondence # 3 7/1/1993 - 11/30/1993 (Box 24)
  - General Correspondence # 2 4/1/1992 - 6/30/1993 (Box 24)
  - General Correspondence # 1 9/1/1990 - 2/29/1992 (Box 24)
  - Program Committee File # 1 6/24/1992 - 5/31/1992 (Box 24)
- Project Management - Quality Assurance
  - Planning and Construction Profile Surveys 1/1992 (Box 24)
  - Evaluation Scoring 6/1990 - 7/1990 (Box 24)
  - General Correspondence # 1 4/9/1990 - 2/25/1991 (Box 24)
  - Heery Program Management General Correspondence 8/9/1990 - 8/10/1990 (Box 24)
  - Heery Program Management Contract File (draft copy) 4/9/1990 (Box 24)
  - Morrison Knudsen General Correspondence 10/31/1991 - 8/29/1996 (Box 24)
  - Morrison Knudsen Contract File CO10465 10/29/1990 - 2/18/1993 (Box 24)
  - Morrison Knudsen Letter Log 3/7/1991 - 5/23/1991 (Box 24)
  - Morrison Knudsen General Correspondence # 1 7/1/1990 - 2/29/1992 (Box 24)
- Records, Maintenance Materials, Storage, and Recycling
  - Budget Spring, 1991 - 12/12/1995 (Box 24)
  - Environmental Impact Statement 5/3/1992 - 7/26/1993 (Box 24)
  - Regents 5/26/1992 - 1/26/1996 (Box 24)
  - Attorney General Correspondence 3/6/1996 RESTRICTED (Box 24)
  - Burke/Lee Correspondence 7/9/1991 - 8/25/1992 (Box 24)
  - Mahan Partnership Correspondence 11/18/1992 - 1/26/1993 (Box 24)
  - Professional Services Industries, Inc. Correspondence 11/15/1994 - 1/27/1995 (Box 24)
  - The Redicheck Firm Correspondence 6/6/1994 - 6/28/1994 (Box 24)
  - Gifford Consultants Geotechnical Report 11/13/1992 (Box 25)
  - Building Committee Minutes 4/23/1991 - 3/16/1993 (Box 25)
  - Daily Construction Reports 11/10/1994 - 6/30/1995 (Box 25)
  - Concrete Test Reports 6/9/1995 (Box 25)
  - General Correspondence #2 5/1/1994 - 5/14/1996 (Box 25)
  - Archos Corporation General Correspondence #6 6/5/1995 - 5/7/1996 (Box 25)
  - Archos Corporation Contract File #1 CO10803 9/27/1991 - 5/10/1996 (Box 25)
  - Mark Construction, Inc. General Correspondence #1 9/1/1994 - 4/2/1997 (Box 25)
  - Mark Construction, Inc. Contract File #1 CO11804 9/1/1994 - 11/6/1995 (Box 25)
  - Pending Change Proposals 12/20/1994 - 11/8/1995 (Box 25)
  - Rejected Bids - Bid Date 9/13/1994 (Box 25)
  - General Correspondence #1 2/1/1995 - 5/31/1995 (Box 25)
  - Archos Corporation General Correspondence #5 7/1/1994 - 1/31/1995 (Box 25)
  - Archos Corporation General Correspondence #4 7/1/1994 - 1/31/1995 (Box 25)
  - Archos Corporation General Correspondence #3 6/1/1994 - 6/31/1994 (Box 25)
  - Archos Corporation General Correspondence #2 10/1/1993 - 5/31/1994 (Box 25)
  - Archos Corporation General Correspondence #1 6/1/1991 - 9/30/1993 (Box 25)